hdvconnect.com 2005-04-03

# Privacy Policy

**Effective July 1, 2004 **

CineForm does not collect personally identifiable information about you, except when you provide it to us. For example, if you decide to complete a user registration form or survey, you may be asked to provide certain information such as your contact information (name, e-mail address, mailing address, and telephone number), gender, birth date and product serial number. If you decide to place an order, we also need to know your delivery and billing address, credit card number and expiration date. To protect your personal information, users registering to use certain parts of our web site may also be required to enter a user name and password.

When you submit your personally identifiable information on this Web site, you are giving your consent to the collection, use and disclosure of your personal information as set forth in this Privacy Policy. If you would prefer that we not collect any personally identifiable information from you, please do not provide us with any such information.

The information you provide may be used by us to create and deliver to you our newsletters, catalogs or surveys, or other communications containing product information, promotions or information concerning your order.

We may use the information you provide in aggregate form for internal business purposes, such as generating statistics and developing marketing plans. We will not sell or rent your personally identifiable information to third parties without your consent, except as disclosed in this Privacy Policy.

We may collect, store or accumulate certain non-personally identifiable information concerning your use of this Web site, such as information regarding which of our pages are most popular.  We may share or transfer such non-personally identifiable information with or to our affiliates, licensees, business partners and other third parties.

We may disclose any information, including personally identifiable information we deem necessary, in our sole discretion, to comply with any applicable law, regulation, legal process or governmental request.  We may also exchange information, including personally identifiable information, with other companies and organizations for credit fraud protection and risk reduction.

We may place a "cookie" on your computer's hard drive so we can recognize you as a return user and personalize your experience.  A cookie is a piece of data that enables us to track and target your preferences.  The cookie will be stored on your computer's hard drive until you remove it. We may also use temporary or "session" cookies to help you shop. These cookies will expire when you leave the Web site. You can have your browser notify you of, or automatically reject, cookies. If you reject our cookies, you may still use our Web site, but you may be limited in the use of some of the features. Some of our business partners may also use cookies on our Web site. However, we have no access to, or control over, these cookies and do not accept any responsibility for such use.

In addition, we may use IP addresses to analyze trends, administer our Web site, track traffic patterns, and gather demographic information for aggregate use, as well as for credit fraud protection and risk reduction. Except as otherwise disclosed in this Privacy Policy, we will not use IP addresses in combination with your personally identifiable information without your prior consent.

When you visit this Web site or view one of our e-mails, we may use pixel tags (also called "clear GIFS" or "clear graphics interchange formats"), tracking links and/or similar technology to note some of the pages you visit on our Web site and personalize your experience. We may also use pixel tags to determine what types of e-mail your browser supports.  We may use the information collected through pixel tags, tracking links and similar technology in combination with your personally identifiable information.

We may retain other companies and individuals to perform functions on our behalf. Examples include ecommerce providers, credit card and shipping fulfillment companies, customer support specialists, and data analysis firms.  Such third parties may be provided with access to personally identifiable information needed to perform their functions, but may not use such information for any other purpose.

This Web site may contain links to or from other Web sites. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the privacy practices of other Web sites. This Privacy Policy applies only to the information we collect on this Web site. We encourage you to read the privacy policies of other Web sites you link to from our Web site or otherwise visit.

As we continue to develop our business, we might sell certain of our assets. In such transactions, user information, including personally identifiable information, generally is one of the transferred business assets, and by submitting your personal information on the Web site you agree that your data may be transferred to such parties in these circumstances.

We may revise this Privacy Policy from time to time. If we decide to change our Privacy Policy, we will post the revised policy here with the effective date specified at the top of the page. As we may make changes at any time we suggest that you periodically review this Privacy Policy. Please note that our rights to use your personally identifiable information will be based on the privacy policy in effect at the time the information is collected.

You have the ability to review, change and correct the personally identifiable information you provide us. If you are a registered user, you can change your personally identifiable information at any time by logging into your account and making required changes.  If you are a registered user, you may also request that we remove from our databases the information you provided when you registered at the Web site, by e-mailing us at [privacy@cineform.com](mailto:privacy@cineform.com).  If you are not a registered user, but have provided personally identifiable information to us, you may also request removal from our database by e-mailing us at [privacy@cineform.com](mailto:privacy@cineform.com).

When you register or place an order at this Web site, you may opt out of receiving future e-mail communications from us. You may change your e-mail preferences at any time by revising your profile, clicking the "unsubscribe" link at the bottom of each e-mail you receive from us and following the instructions provided or, if you do not have a profile, by e-mailing us at [privacy@cineform.com](mailto:privacy@cineform.com)
